<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- https://github.com/snaptortoise/jekyll-rss-feeds -->
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Ryan Johnson&#39;s Posts</title>
        <description>Computer Science and other things.</description>      
        <link>http://ryanxjohnson.com/posts/</link>
        <atom:link href="http://ryanxjohnson.com/posts//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>First Job</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;I start my first developer job in a few weeks. This is exciting, because this is why my end goal was going into college. I’ve been brushing up on C# and JavaScript over the past couple of weeks so I can be productive starting out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wish me luck.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2015 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
            <link>http://ryanxjohnson.com/posts//posts/2015/11/11/FirstJob/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ryanxjohnson.com/posts//posts/2015/11/11/FirstJob/</guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Where to Start</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;As a new grad, it’s slightly overwhelming to pick a technology and become an expert in it. Not only are there many technologies, but the complexity and relevance of each differs. I appreciate the things tech can do, and I’m determined to find out what I can do. I’m like a kid in a toy store, but the toys are complex and will shoot you in the foot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In college, we not only learned Computer Science theory, but engaged with current technology and created technology. In one Software Engineering course, we even had a real customer with real system requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s easy to become exposed to many technologies in a short time frame, which I have done. Now it’s up to me to determine my path. How can I best contribute to the tech world? Is it embedded software, back-end database design, software architecture, or even UI? Should I focus on Web Applications or Mobile friendly? Should I involve hardware into my creations or strictly software? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll keep up with learning while I am looking for my first developer job.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
            <link>http://ryanxjohnson.com/posts//posts/2015/03/06/WhereToStart/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ryanxjohnson.com/posts//posts/2015/03/06/WhereToStart/</guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
